### Lisa Witkowski

2700 Cypress Ave Los Angeles, CA 90065 github.com/lswitkowski

#### **About Me**

I've built a restaurant leadership career on teamwork, logistics, problem-solving, and delivering exceptional experiences under pressure. I now craft responsive, user-friendly, and visually appealing websites and applications with JavaScript, Bootstrap, and React. I'm an enthusiastic, self-motivated learner, but will benefit from objectives, standards and mentorship that come from working on a team.

## Tools I'm Learning to Use & Tools I'm Using to Learn

SheCodes Bootcamp: structured learning that covered html, css, bootstrap, JavaScript, VSCode, API, NPM, GitHub, Hosting, AI, Python, Data Structures, React.js.

freeCodeCamp: I'm currently working through the core curriculum to reinforce and expand on the basics.

# **Experience**

Rustic Canyon / General Manager & Sommelier May 2023 - Jan 2024, Santa Monica, CA

Perle / General Manager & Sommelier June 2021 - May 2023, Pasadena, CA

Petit Trois Le Valley / Assistant Manager & Bar Manager May 2019 - May 2021, Los Angeles, CA

Montrésor / The Flats / General Manager & Operations Dec 2017-May 2019, Studio City/ Beverly Hills, CA

Beaubourg at Le District / Manager Oct 2015 - Nov 2017, New York, NY

The Brooklyn Kitchen / Classroom Coordinator October 2012 to April 2014, New York, NY

Le Manoir aux Quat' Saisons / Cookery School Tutor February 2007 - September 2011, Great Milton, Oxfordshire, UK

### Education

**SUNY Oneonta** | B.S. Political Science

- University College London, School of Slavonic and Eastern European Studies -Hungarian Language and Literature
- Boğaziçi University Turkish & Middle Eastern Studies
- University College Dublin Irish Studies
   Summer Session

International Culinary Center / French
Culinary Institute | Grand diplôme Culinary
Arts

International Culinary Center / French Culinary Institute | Advanced Sommelier Studies

### Other Features

English - Native, French- C1, Court of Master Sommeliers - Certified, Certified Cicerone, United States & EU Citizen